fbadsexposed.com 2010-11-20

# Facebook Ads Exposed - Order Page

organization or used by the site itself for product design or solicitation purposes.

**INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM ELECTRONIC MEANS AND 'COOKIES'**

Many websites, including this one, collect information about your computer, your email address, your IP address.  You must assume that your web-viewing or web-use activity is monitored, tracked, and information collected.  This information is not usually of a personal nature, but it may help define your viewing habits and product preferences even though the website may or may not have any idea who you are.

"Cookies" is web jargon for bits of computer code placed on your hard drive.  Websites use this to keep you 'logged in', to keep track of search criteria, to monitor use, to password protect use of the site or use of products sold by the site.  Cookies can also be used to obtain information about your computer configuration or your use of your computer.

Cookies can be used to electronically gather information about you.  Again, it may or may not be personal information, but it is information and by using this site you are expressly giving permission to use 'cookies' and to use the information gathered from their use to benefit you.  You also give permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and use any information collected for product design, product offers to you, and general commercial solicitation purposes by this site or joint venture partners, affiliates, and marketing organizations.

**HOW INFORMATION MAY BE USED**

The use of information as described below may or may not be how information that is collected is customarily used by this site.  While actual use of any information collected may be used quite conservatively, you must assume that it is not.  You must assume that information collected is shared with other persons or entities for commercial purposes.  While this may or may not occur, you must assume that it is as you make your decision whether or not to view or interact with this website.  This type of shared information may include your name, address, phone number, email address and buying habits, as well as other information.  This information may be used for general commercial solicitation by this website or other persons it is sold to, rented to, or shared with.

**INFORMATION THAT IS NOT SHARED**

Credit card information or other financial information is not usually known to the website.  However, in the event that it is made known, that information is never revealed to anyone except to processing authorities or law enforcement agencies.  However, the provider of such information gives express permission to use it in fraud investigation or for litigation.

**BULLETIN BOARDS AND PUBLIC FORUMS**

Visitors, subscribers, members, or customers who use any site provided bulletin boards or other public forums, such as chat rooms, do so at their own risk.  You may not assume that the site monitors these services or protects you in any manner from information you post publicly or share with anyone else via these services.

**SPAM  **

By providing to this website information that forms the basis of communication with you, such as an email address, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email or spam from this website since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us or other marketing organizations.  However, all email communication with you shall contain an 'unsubscribe' link where you may notify the website that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information from the website and your name will be removed from the general solicitation database.

**DATA SECURITY**

This website takes measures to protect its data that contains information related to you.  However, as a consideration for viewing this site or interacting with this site in any manner, you waive all claims of any nature against this site concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of information.  You must assume that it is possible for your personal data to be obtained by others, such as "hackers," and used in an inappropriate manner that may cause you harm and that you agree that the site is not responsible for damages to you.

**REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WITHOUT NOTICE**

This Privacy Policy is dynamic.  It will continually change.  You may not assume that it remains the same and you agree to check the policy each time you visit the site for changes.  Unless, in the sole opinion of the website, this policy changes so drastically as to suggest a posted notification on the site or via email, you will receive no notification of changes to this Privacy Policy nor, under any circumstances, does this site promise notification.  Your continued use of this site always evidences your acceptance of the terms this Privacy Policy or any modifications.

**DISPUTES**

As part of the consideration that the Website requires of the Visitor to view, use, or interact with this site, Visitor agrees to use binding arbitration for any claim, dispute, or controversy ("CLAIM") of any kind (whether in contract, tort or otherwise) arising out of or relating to this purchase, this product, including solicitation issues, privacy issues, and terms of use issues.

Arbitration shall be conducted pursuant to the rules of the American Arbitration Association, which are in effect on the date a dispute is submitted to the American Arbitration Association.  Information about the American Arbitration Association, its rules, and its forms are available from the American Arbitration Association, 335 Madison Avenue, Floor 10, New York, New York, 10017-4605.  Hearing will take place in the city or county of the Seller. 

In no case shall the Visitor have the right to go to court or have a jury trial.  Visitor will not have the right to engage in pre-trial discovery except as provided in the rules; you will not have the right to participate as a representative or member of any class of claimants pertaining to any claim subject to arbitration; the arbitrator's decision will final and binding with limited rights of appeal. 

The prevailing party shall be reimbursed by the other party for any and all costs associated with the dispute arbitration, including attorney fees, collection fees, investigation fees, travel expenses.

**JURISDICTION AND VENUE**

If any matter concerning this purchase shall be brought before a court of law, pre- or post-arbitration, Visitor agrees to that the sole and proper jurisdiction to be the state and city declared in the contact information of the web owner unless otherwise here specified. In the event that litigation is in a federal court, the proper court shall be the closest federal court to the Seller's address.

**APPLICABLE LAW**

Visitor agrees that the applicable law to be applied shall, in all cases, be that of the state of the Website owner(s). 

_________________________________________________________________________

Copyright 2010 FBAdsExposed.com - All rights reserved.

Home | [Contact Support](mailto:support@fbadsexposed.com) | Order Now! | Disclaimer | Privacy | Affiliate Earn Cash
